<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Hana Kalpak</title>
    <link>/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Hana Kalpak</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021 Hana Kalpak</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/about/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;
I&amp;rsquo;m a PhD student in philosophy at Stockholm University, specialized in formal epistemology and semantics. I think and write about rational belief, rational inquiry, and the relation between the two.
I started as a PhD student in February, 2019. Before this, I got a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in logic from University of Amsterdam in 2018, and a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in philosophy (with a minor in linguistics) from Stockholm University in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>projects</title>
      <link>/home/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/projects/</guid>
      <description>Feel free to email me for drafts or discussion.
Decision rules for imprecise Lockeans I outline some ways to establish a utility-theoretic Lockean thesis connecting our rational beliefs to our rational imprecise credences.
Relevance and the aim of inquiry I develop a relevance-first theory of rational inquiry, and relate it to accuracy-first theories of rational belief/credence.
Question-sensitive beliefs and question-sensitive contents In a certain sense, our beliefs are question-sensitive. I reason about how this assumption should (not) affect our semantics of belief reports as well as our general theory of communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selected Publications</title>
      <link>/home/publications_selected/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/publications_selected/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>papers</title>
      <link>/home/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/publications/</guid>
      <description>2021 Factive islands and interrogative logical triviality. PDF Proceedings of Semantics and Linguistic Theory 30.
2020 The semantics and pragmatics of nouns in concealed questions. PDF Semantics &amp;amp; Pragmatics 13(7).
2019 Sortal versus relational nouns in concealed questions. Proceedings of Chicago Linguistic Society 54. Superseded by The semantics and pragmatics of nouns in concealed questions.
Inquisitive logical triviality and grammar. PDF MSc thesis, University of Amsterdam. Partially superseded by Unacceptability in Yucatec Maya revisited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>talks</title>
      <link>/home/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/talks/</guid>
      <description>2022 Decision rules for imprecise Lockeans. Slides Talk at CLLAM seminar, Stockholm University, March 2022.
2020 Delusions and other question-sensitive beliefs. Handout Talk at fifth PLM workshop on Delusions in language and mind, University of Amsterdam (on-line), October 2020.
Factive islands and interrogative logical triviality. Slides Talk at SALT 30, Cornell University (on-line), August 2020.
2019 Sources of meaning-driven unacceptability. Abstract Talk at Principles of Formal Semantics, Stockholm University, September 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent Posts</title>
      <link>/home/posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/posts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>teaching</title>
      <link>/home/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/teaching/</guid>
      <description>For courses taught as instructor or assistant, see my CV.
Metod - Argumentation, semantik och formell logik. 2020, 2021. Gavs som del av Teoretisk Filosofi I.
Slides - Kursdel I
Argument I Argument II Mängdlära Semantik I Semantik II Semantik III Repetition I
Slides - Kursdel II
Satslogik I Satslogik II Satslogik III Predikatlogik I Predikatlogik II Predikatlogik III Repetition II</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tags</title>
      <link>/home/tags/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/tags/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>contact</title>
      <link>/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/contact/</guid>
      <description>For current physical address, see my CV.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>